<?xml version="1.0"?>
        <rss xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
        <channel>
        <title>Wigme Store</title>
        <description>Product Feed for Facebook</description>
         <link rel="self" href="http://wigme.com/">
<item>
                <g:item_group_id>GCR6057</g:item_group_id>
                <g:id>None</g:id>
                <g:title>Geepas GCR6057 Free Standing Cooking Range, 60x60</g:title>
                <g:description>Geepas 60 Free Standing Cooking Range, 60x60, with Double Knobs Control Separately System, Push Button Ignition Top Gas Burners will help you in easy use of Geepas Free Standing Cooking.This Geepas Free Standing Cooking Range, 60x60 has a clean and simple design, it's super easy for anyone to get to grips with to do some quality cooking, plus it offers excellent value for money. With a Double Layer Brown Rock Wool Instruction this neat cooker gives you the best of both. The gas hob provides instant heat with precise control, whilst the electric ovens deliver even and reliable cooking. The hob features four burners in an array of sizes to suit different pots and pan sizes.The design comes in great whether you're cooking for one or the full family. The bottom main oven offers fan assisted cooking, so heat is evenly distributed throughout, meaning no matter where you place a dish inside it will be evenly cooked to perfection. It comes in great for extra oven space when you're cooking up a feast or when you're cooking for one, saving you time heating a smaller oven whilst saving energy. Upgrade your kitchen with one of the safe and reliable cooking ranges. Featuring a smart and practical design, each product will lighten your burden and make cooking a pleasurable process by providing you multi-functional benefits. Sturdy and equipped with state of the art technology, these cooking ranges are a must-have to complete your kitchen. </g:description>
                <g:link>https://www.wigme.com/product-description-new/b4bbdd77-451f-4242-9bf0-e589583e13e1</g:link>
                <g:image_link>https://wig-wams-s3-bucket.s3.amazonaws.com/download_0ghJCkQ.jpeg</g:image_link>
                <g:condition>new</g:condition>
                <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
                <g:price>0.0 AED</g:price>
                <g:mpn>None</g:mpn>
                <g:brand>Geepas</g:brand>
                </entry>
<item>
                <g:item_group_id>GRF1259GPE</g:item_group_id>
                <g:id>1234567899123</g:id>
                <g:title>Geepas 125L DoubleDoor silver Defrost Refrigerator1x1</g:title>
                <g:description>The DoubleDoor silver Defrost Refrigerator under-counter fridge with chill box is apt for households, student accommodation and office environments where space is a premium. It has been designed to fit neatly under the counter and has adjustable feet to keep it stable on any service, with reversible doors for versatility. It comes with internal light, adjustable leg.</g:description>
                <g:link>https://www.wigme.com/product-description-new/b332b161-cdfb-468b-bfb9-4e12515337cc</g:link>
                <g:image_link>https://wig-wams-s3-bucket.s3.amazonaws.com/download_0ghJCkQ.jpeg</g:image_link>
                <g:condition>new</g:condition>
                <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
                <g:price>100.0 AED</g:price>
                <g:mpn>1234567899123</g:mpn>
                <g:brand>Geepas</g:brand>
                </entry>
</channel></rss>
